Guide to the Philip Taietz papers, 1962-2000.
Taietz, Philip papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Philip Taietz papers, 1962-2000.
21-33-3727
Taietz, Philip
.5 cubic foot
Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes Taietz's publications and results of a 1993 survey "Factors Associated with Continued Professional Productivity of Emeritus Professors at Cornell University" and a 1998 study "Post-Retirement Productivity and Life Quality of Emeritus Professors."
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes Taietz's publications and results of a 1993 survey "Factors Associated with Continued Professional Productivity of Emeritus Professors at Cornell University" and a 1998 study "Post-Retirement Productivity and Life Quality of Emeritus Professors."
SUBJECTS
Names:
Taietz, Philip; Cornell Univeristy--Faculty; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.Dept. of Rural Sociology
Subjects:
Older people--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Articles by Philip Taietz, 1953-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Statements from Taitz's Memorial Service, June 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Emeritus Professors contacted in study "Factors Associated with Continued Professional Effectiveness in Emeritus Professors at Cornell", 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Letter sent to Emeriti Professors (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Information about the Study Preliminary Report, August 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Survey of Cornell Emeriti Who Have Moved From Ithaca #101-122 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Survey of Cornell Emeriti Who Have Moved From Ithaca #126-145 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Survey of Cornell Emeriti Who Have Moved From Ithaca #146-166 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Survey of Cornell Emeriti Who Have Moved From Ithaca #167-190 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Survey of Cornell Emeriti Who Have Moved From Ithaca #193-208 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Survey of Cornell Emeriti Who Have Moved From Ithaca #207-305 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Material from study "Post-Retirement Productivity and Life Quality of Emeritus Professors", 1998 (Box 2)